Shaked Ben Yechezkel

I'm third year student of computer science in the College of Management Academic Studies. Determined to learn and hungry to succeed in the field of computer science. I am now doing my Cyber specialization.

My final project: Project "WebGate", a firewall designed to be smart and affordable. Created for the average household to provide constant and reliable network monitoring and security with minimal knowledge and tinkering.

Education:

2018- present: 3RD year **Computer Science student (B.Sc.)**, The College of Academic Management Studies, Rishon Le Zion.

2010-2013: "Amit Hamal" high school, Majored in Physics and Biology.

Professional Skills:

C, C++, Java, Python, JavaScript, CSS, Html, SQL, Data structures, Algorithm, Advanced Microsoft Excel, Application development course.

Work Experience:

2019-Covid-19: Working as a hostess at "Lian productions Ltd".

2017-2019: Kindergarten teacher assistant at "Gan Ofarim".

Army Service:

2015-2017: Classified role at the Ministry of Defense.

Working under pressure, full availability, high responsibility and assertiveness.

Language Skills:

Hebrew - Native language, English – Proficient.

Personal Characteristics:

Responsible, a quick learner, a team player and punctual. The ability to work under pressure.